Brown, Fred R.; Papers mss004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- University of Amoy, 1931; Undated; 11
  Letters regarding study at the Summer Institute; article on the Amoy earthworm; statement by the faculty and staff regarding the Japanese invasion of Manchuria.
  - University of Amoy. Summer Institute of Biological Research, Undated (Box 3 (11-University of Amoy), Folder 82)
  - "Anatomy of Pheretima aspergillum..." by Shao-Wen Ling, Undated (Box 3 (11-University of Amoy), Folder 83)
  - "On the Tenth Anniversary of the Foundation of the University of Amoy", Undated (Box 3 (11-University of Amoy), Folder 84)
  - "A Manifesto on the Japanese Invasion of Manchuria. Issued by the Faculty and Staff of the University of Amoy, Amoy, China", 1931 (Box 3 (11-University of Amoy), Folder 85)
  - Zhu Nianzu's Statement of Exoneration, Undated (Box 3 (11-University of Amoy), Folder 86)
  - 1930 Report on Dr. Kahn's Women's Hospital, plus other reports, Undated (Box 3 (11-University of Amoy), Folder 87)
- Mission Conferences, 1920-1948; 12
  Reports on various conferences from 1920 to 1948.
  - China's Challenge and the Methodist Reply. Program of Advance of the Methodist Episcopal Church in China adopted at the Program Study and Statement Conference, Peking, 1920 January 27-1920 February 10 (Box 4 (12-Mission Conferences), Folder 1)
  - National Christian Conference, Shanghai, 1922 (Box 4 (12-Mission Conferences), Folder 2)
  - Report of a Conference of Christian Workers with Dr. John R. Mott..., 1926 January 5-7 (Box 4 (12-Mission Conferences), Folder 3)
  - Kiangsi Annual Conference, Undated; 12.4 (Box 4 (12-Mission Conferences), Folder 4)
    - a. Twelfth, 1928
    - b. Thirteenth, 1929
    - c. Fourteenth, 1930
    - d. Fifteenth, 1931
    - e. Sixteenth, 1932
    - f. Seventeenth, 1933
    - g. Eighteenth, 1934
    - h. Nineteenth, 1935
    - i. Twentieth, 1936
  - Kiangsi Annual Conference, 1940; 1948 (Box 4 (12-Mission Conferences), Folder 5)
  - Kiangsi Women's Conference, 1934-1935 (Box 4 (12-Mission Conferences), Folder 6)
  - Kiangsi Conference: Miscellaneous items, Undated (Box 4 (12-Mission Conferences), Folder 7)
  - Eastern Asia Central Conference, 1930 (Box 4 (12-Mission Conferences), Folder 8)
  - Eastern Asia Central Conference, 1934; 1937 (Box 4 (12-Mission Conferences), Folder 9)
- Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S., 1936-1961; 13
  Religious teaching and preaching of FRB after his return to the United States. Includes sermon notes and other devotional material.
  - Bible Study...; Bible-reading calendar, Undated (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 10)
  - Order of Service, 1938-1944 (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 11)
  - Notebook, 1938-1957 (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 11)
  - Sermon Topics, Readings, Text, 1944-1954 (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 11)
  - "Cycle of Prayer...", 1939 November 21 (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 12)
  - "Holy Week, Midday Service", 1940 March 22 (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 13)
  - "Sermons on the Apostles' Creed", 1940 April-1940 September (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 14)
  - "Hymns, Readings, Attendance. Fonda & Fultonville, 1944-1948 (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 15)
  - "Sermon Outlines", 1943-1944 (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 16)
  - Revelation, 1947 (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 17)
  - "JOB", 1948 January-1948 February (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 18)
  - "Spiritual Diary for Lent", 1953 (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 19)
  - "Revelation", 1961 (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 20)
  - "Sermon Notes", Undated; 13.14
    - 1936 November-1937 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 21)
    - 1938 January-1938 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 22)
    - 1939 January-1939 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 23)
    - 1940 January-1940 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 24)
    - 1941 January-1941 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 25)
    - 1942 January-1942 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 26)
    - 1943 January-1943 June (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 27)
    - 1943 July-1943 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 28)
    - 1944 January-1944 June (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 29)
    - 1944 July-1944 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 30)
    - 1945 January-1945 June (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 31)
    - 1945 July-1945 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 32)
    - 1946 January-1946 June (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 33)
    - 1946 July-1946 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 34)
    - 1947 January-1947 June (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 35)
    - 1947 July-1947 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 36)
    - 1948 January-1948 June (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 37)
    - 1948 July-1948 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 38)
    - 1949 January-1949 June (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 39)
    - 1949 July-1949 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 40)
    - 1950 January-1950 June (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 41)
    - 1950 July-1950 December (Box 4 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 42)
    - 1951 January-1951 June (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 1)
    - 1951 July-1951 December (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 2)
    - 1952 January-1952 June (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 3)
    - 1952 July-1952 December (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 4)
    - 1953 January-1953 June (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 5)
    - 1953 July-1953 December (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 6)
    - 1954 January-1954 June (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 7)
    - 1954 July-1954 December (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 8)
    - 1955 January-1955 June (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 9)
    - 1955 July-1955 December (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 10)
    - 1956 January-1956 June (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 11)
    - 1956 July-1956 December (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 12)
    - 1957 January-1957 June (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 13)
    - 1957 July-1957 December (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 14)
    - 1958 January-1958 June (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 15)
    - 1958 July-1958 December (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 16)
    - 1959 January-1959 June (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 17)
    - 1959 July-1959 December (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 18)
    - 1960 January-1960 June (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 19)
    - 1960 July-1960 December (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 20)
    - 1961 January-1961 May (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 21)
    - Sample covers for "Sermon Notes" (Box 5 (13-Religious Teaching and Preaching in the U.S.), Folder 22)
- Church and Teaching Activities, 1937-1961; 14
  Church notices, parish histories, religious and science instruction materials. Covers the period 1937 to 1961. (The Church Notices include letters from the Troy Conference.).
  - Church notices, 1945 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 23)
  - Church notices, 1946 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 24)
  - Church notices, 1951-1961 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 25)
  - Certificate of Membership blanks, Undated (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 26)
  - Funerals, Undated (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 27)
  - General Conference, 1944 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 28)
  - Methodist parish histories, 1939 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 29)
  - "Copy for Historical Booklet: Troy", 1939 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 30)
  - Church affairs: Schaghticoke, N.Y., 1947-1948 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 31)
  - International Council of Religious Education, 1950 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 32)
  - Clarksville Methodist Church, 1952-1957 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 33)
  - Clarksville Church Centenary, 1957 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 34)
  - Clinical pastoral training, Albany Hospital, 1956-1957 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 35)
  - Embury-Heck Anniversary Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 36)
  - Missionary education material, 1937 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 37)
  - Instructional aids: Pastors Seminars: How to Teach, Undated (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 38)
  - Religious instruction: Released time classes, 1950-1951; 1951-1952 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 39)
  - Geology, Botany, Paleontology notes, 1932 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 40)
  - Geology and Astronomy notes, 1938-1941 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 41)
  - Math methods, 1932 (Box 5 (14-Church and Teaching Activities), Folder 42)
- Troy Conference of the Methodist Board of Missions, 1945-1965; 15
  Correspondence, notes, reports, newspaper clippings, and issues of the Official Journal of the Troy Annual Conference; a copy of the condensed annual report of the Board of Missions of the Methodist Church.
  - Troy Annual Conference: Daily proceedings, 1945 (Box 6 (15-Troy Conference of the Methodist Board of Missions), Folder 1)
  - Troy Conference Board of Missions, 1951-1954 (Box 6 (15-Troy Conference of the Methodist Board of Missions), Folder 2)
  - Troy Conference Board of Missions: Scratch minutes, duplicates, etc., 1952-1953 (Box 6 (15-Troy Conference of the Methodist Board of Missions), Folder 3)
  - Troy Methodist Conference, 1962 (Box 6 (15-Troy Conference of the Methodist Board of Missions), Folder 4)
  - Troy Annual Conference: General insurance report, 1964 (Box 6 (15-Troy Conference of the Methodist Board of Missions), Folder 5)
  - Troy Annual Conference: Ministerial appointments, 1965 (Box 6 (15-Troy Conference of the Methodist Board of Missions), Folder 6)
  - Troy Conference: Miscellaneous items, 1951; 1958 (Box 6 (15-Troy Conference of the Methodist Board of Missions), Folder 7)
  - Troy Conference Historical Society, Undated (Box 6 (15-Troy Conference of the Methodist Board of Missions), Folder 8)
  - Official Journal of the Troy Annual Conference of The Methodist Church, Undated; 15.9 (Box 6 (15-Troy Conference of the Methodist Board of Missions), Folder 9)
    - a., 1947
    - b., 1949
    - c., 1950
    - d., 1951
    - e., 1952
    - f., 1953
    - g., 1957; 15.9.7
      - Methodist Church: Board of Missions and Church Extension -Condensed Annual Report, 1953 (Box 6 (15.9.7-g.), Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous, 1925-1940; 16
  FRB's lecture notes and writings on various subjects; writings by others; items in Chinese.
  - FRB. "A Critical Exposition of Bertrand Russell's Views on Religion", Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 11)
  - FRB. "Errors in Language Made by Natick [Mass.] Elementary Grade Pupils", 1925 (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 12)
  - FRB. [Notes on] "Lectures on Present Tendencies", Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 13)
  - FRB. "A Visit to the Synagogue", 1940 May 27 (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 14)
  - Calendar for 1929, 1930 (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 15)
  - Monetary Exchange, 1927-1928 (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 16)
  - Howe, Gertrude [biographical sketch, account of her work], Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 17)
  - Kahn, Ida [clippings, pamphlet], Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 18)
  - Biddle, Francis. "Communism", Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 19)
  - Cotton, Edward H. "Woodrow Wilson's Religion", Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 20)
  - Chen, William H., trans. "Personal Hygiene for Nurses", Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 21)
  - Douglas, A. Vibert. "From Atoms to Stars", Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 22)
  - Jordan, L. E. "From Confucianism to Christ", Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 23)
  - Mac Tavish & Lehmann, Limited. "Signs of the Times", Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 24)
  - Stewart, Charles D. "The Tree as an Invention", Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 25)
  - Van Dusen, H. P. Methodism's World Mission [summary of Chapter Five on India], Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 26)
  - Items in Chinese, Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 27)
  - Books in Chinese (7); English - Japanese dictionary, Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous items, Undated (Box 6 (16-Miscellaneous), Folder 29)
- Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown), 1912-1949; 17
  Biographical materials on CMB and her family; correspondence; kindergarten and religious instruction materials; stories (most written as class assignments); student essays and class notes for Syracuse University courses.
  - Biographical material, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 30)
  - Letter of introduction from Bishop Birney, 1924 (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 31)
  - Letters home, diary, 1912-1914 (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 32)
  - Letters to family, 1949 (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 33)
  - Letters from family and friends, 1920-1948 (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 34)
  - Kindergarten instruction, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 35)
  - Kindergarten instruction, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 36)
  - Kindergarten, instruction, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 37)
  - Religious instruction, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 38)
  - Religious instruction, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 39)
  - Religious instruction - Notes, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 40)
  - Religious instruction - Pictures, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 41)
  - "Gifts", "Occupations" [notebooks], Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 42)
  - Notes for lectures, etc., Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 43)
  - [Political situation in China] - Notes, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 44)
  - "The Angel and the Assistant", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 45)
  - "Building the Kingdom", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 46)
  - "The Cradle of Liberty", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 47)
  - "The Disarmament Conference", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 48)
  - "The Doctor's Assistant", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 49)
  - "Education of Man", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 50)
  - "The Farewell to the Kerns", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 51)
  - "Hope is Dead - Long Live Hope", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 52)
  - "Lao Lan", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 53)
  - "Life of Fredrich Froebel", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 54)
  - "New Testament", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 55)
  - "Schools of 1850 & 1900", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 56)
  - "The Story of Creation", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 57)
  - "What is Chapel (to an Inhabitant of Mars)", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 58)
  - "What Price Reputation", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 59)
  - "Which", Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 60)
  - Student papers, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 61)
  - Manuscript from looseleaf folder, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 62)
  - Class assignments; tests, 1932 (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 63)
  - Transcript, Syracuse University, 1932 (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 64)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6 (17-Clella Ernestine McDonnell (Mrs. Fred R. Brown)), Folder 65)
- Photographs and Maps, 1888-1966; 18
  Mainly family photographs, but also includes the Atlas of Foreign Missions, maps, drawings, and notebook pages.
  - Atlas of Foreign Missions. New York: Board of Foreign Missions of the Methodist Episcopal Church, [1909] (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 1)
  - Map: Kiangsi, China, 1934 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 2)
  - Map: Kingtehchen, drawn by Rawlinson J. Ku, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 3)
  - Map: China, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 4)
  - Map: Poyang Lake, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 5)
  - Maps: Nanchang City; the Kan River District; the Kienchang District, 1911; Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 6)
  - Maps: Shanghai, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 7)
  - Maps: China and Japan, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 8)
  - Maps: Manchuria, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 9)
  - Maps: Syracuse, Boston, Paris, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 10)
  - Leese, Holly. "Mission Zeal in China: The Brown Papers", 1974 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 11)
  - Notebook pages of Clella M. Brown, [1931?] (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 12)
  - Notebook pages of Clella M. Brown, [1932] (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 13)
  - Notebook pages of Clella M. Brown, [1932] (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 14)
  - Pastel drawing of Chinese Landscape by Clella E. Brown, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Mr. and Mrs. John M. McDonnell (Clella's parents), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Clella E. McDonnell (approx. age 2), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 17)
  - Photograph: Clella E. McDonnell (6th or 7h grade), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 18)
  - Photograph: Clella E. McDonnell (age 16, high school graduation), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 19)
  - Photographs: Clella E. McDonnell (group photos, one dated 1908), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 20)
  - Photographs: Clella E. McDonnell and friends at Hyland Park College, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 21)
  - Photographs: Clella E. McDonnell and missionaries on the S.S. Manchuria, 1912 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 22)
  - Clipping: "Methodist Missionaries Now Here Soon To Go Abroad"The Baltimore News, 1912 October 27 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 23)
  - Photographs: Clella E. McDonnell and friends (China, pre-1914), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 24)
  - Photographs: Charles Victor McDonnell and family (Clella's brother), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 25)
  - Photographs: Goodwin McDonnell and family (Clella's brother), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 26)
  - Photographs: Oscar Lewis McDonnell and family (Clella's brother), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 27)
  - Photographs: Elcina Tracy and family (Clella's sister), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 28)
  - Photographs: Clella McDonnell Shaffer and family (Clella's niece), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 29)
  - Photographs: Bernice Helen McDonnell Dodge and family (Clella's niece), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 30)
  - Photographs: Fallgetters (Clella's cousins), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 31)
  - Photographs: Gertrude McDonnell Robertson and family (Clella's cousin), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 32)
  - Photographs: McDonnell Family (miscellaneous photos), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 33)
  - Photographs: McDonnell Family (unidentified photos), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 34)
  - Photographs: Mr. and Mrs. Edgar H. Brown and family (Fred's parents), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 35)
  - Photographs: Fred R. Brown, 1888-1889 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 36)
  - Photograph: Fred R. Brown (group photo taken in Albany, NY), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 37)
  - Photographs: Fred R. Brown (group photos taken in Syracuse, NY), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 38)
  - Photographs: Fred R. Brown, (wedding 1914) (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 39)
  - Photographs: Fred R. Brown and family, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 40)
  - Photograph and postcard: Beijing, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 41)
  - Photographs and postcards: Kuling (items from Clella's "Post Album"), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 42)
  - Photographs: Kiukiang and Nanchang, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 43)
  - Photograph: Kiukiang Chamber of Commerce closing exercises, ca. 1912 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 44)
  - Photographs and postcards: Nanking, 1912 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 45)
    (items from Clella's "Post Album").
  - Photographs: Nanchang, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 46)
  - Photographs and postcards: Nanchang Academy and Hospital, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 47)
  - Photographs and postcards: Nanchang Women's and Children's Hospital, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 48)
  - Photographs and postcards from the interior of China, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 49)